<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Continue Project</title>
    <link>https://continueproject.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Continue Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:38:58 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://continueproject.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Initial Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://continueproject.com/posts/initial-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:38:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://continueproject.com/posts/initial-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>This project sprang out of seemingly nowhere.
I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about mental health and well-being for all of my adult life. I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about it in the context of my own life and demons, and I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about it with regard to those I love.
It ain&amp;rsquo;t easy.
I feel like my community - that of software developers and engineers - is underserved with regard to mental health and suicide prevention, and so the idea for this project began to form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://continueproject.com/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 11:55:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://continueproject.com/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Life is no simple thing. This project is a recognition of that fact.
It is a recognition that we all - well or ill, successful or still striving - need a hand now and then.
It is to be a source of help, of hope, of inspiration to those in need of it.
We aim to provide resources for and support of initiatives focused on suicide prevention and mental health awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://continueproject.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 11:55:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://continueproject.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Task Live() { while (this.Body.Contains(&amp;#34;Breath&amp;#34;)) continue; } This project was started with the goal of promoting mental health and suicide prevention in the engineering and software development industries. We aim to support a few groups of people:
 Developers and engineers who feel isolated and need support Developers and engineers who want to better support their loved ones in need Loved ones of developers and engineers who don&amp;rsquo;t know how to help  We&amp;rsquo;re just getting started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://continueproject.com/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 11:55:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://continueproject.com/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Continue Project Community Code of Conduct Welcome! The Continue Project is an open community of developers, engineers, and technologists who recognize the importance of mental health in our lives and support each other with resources and space for discussion as colleagues and friends.
We want this to be a fun, pleasant, and harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, or religion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
